To start with,
yesterday evening brother Shahid Bhai from the stock market,
today's preparation for tomorrow's market, the
market has been very good for this week, it is very
better, it is very
wonderful,
it has been very wonderful,
I sometimes think
that after all,
what should be the margin of profit on your capital, by the way,
I myself believe that it is
not a matter of 15-20% because the way
I am in my poverty, to convert it into a big wealth,
I look for those areas,
friends
subscribe and my attention will
turn towards that in a way and take me there, I feel
subscribed and I want that in that, my
efforts have always been made and I
get some success in it and
subscribe, whatever
I have subscribed,
but I am saying that if friends
subscribe, I am
not saying anything
like the eighth wonder and this has not happened
in the stock market and Indian market share market, it is not like that at all,
rather for your information, let me tell you
that last year's
Ravan
Meghnad
Subscribe
Shyam  And
subscribe,
this is so amazingly exciting,
subscribe, I have nothing to do with this,
subscribe just a quarter of an inch from here, I wanted to know two quarters from people,
I said buy TCS like fire,
I ask you to buy with your eyes closed, the
question system, you buy Infosys with your
eyes closed,
subscribe, this is a big question,
when the
scooter runs,
subscribe, if you
subscribe, because I have bought TCS at
crores and I believe in this opportunity very much that
you can take advantage of it, I am
repeating the pairs again
and make purchases in it very carefully, actual
and at such a great price
and the price of the bank has reached during this time through the
buying
drum, remember when I
started Grasim, I said that this is a very
subscribe, what am I thinking,
and
subscribe, you have
subscribe from here and subscribe so that
you must look at it, TCS and Infosys,
I said actual and HDFC, I said
come, from this time of price, ICICI Lombard,
you should buy your real value from its wound  Even more so,
buy ICICI Lombard and Parichay today. There are excellent opportunities.
Remember, I've been telling you about City Union Bank.
You can buy in Shirdi today even at 170.
Buy Torrent Pharma. Buy
Gujarat Gas and IT stocks. Buy
HDFC and HUL.
Buy Power Grid and Petrol Rate.
And finally, I want to say one more thing about
Nashe The Boss, which I
told you about Three Geniuses, did
you achieve success in that? Or you can check out my previous video and
see at what price the Boss was, at
what price the page was there, and at what
price Nestle was there. Well, if there was any rise in it today,
but always remember that you have
subscribed to 2500 banks, so you are
subscribed. But I will definitely comment
that the
youth should
subscribe first and
subscribe. Do some buying in these banks like Kotak Mahindra,
Axis Bank and small banks. If you
want to focus on some banks
where you can stay for a long time, then
stay on Bank of Baroda and Bank of Baroda and
subscribe before
going to the office.  In which there will be
discussion on Tata Motors and Tata Power, there will be
discussion on Tata Motors and Tata Power, that's all
for today, 12 September 2003,
more preparations made for buying in the stock market